let questions = [
    {
        //image 1
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which one of these shapes is most used to represent an ALU? (open Q1 img in new tab)",
    answer: "1",
    options: [
      "1",
      "2",
      "3",
      "4"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is the correct order an instruction takes through a processorâ€™s components?",
    answer: "Instruction Memory -> Control Unit -> Register File -> ALU -> Data Memory",
    options: [
      "Instruction Memory -> ALU -> Register File -> Control Unit -> Data Memory ",
      "Data Memory -> ALU -> Register File -> Control Unit -> Instruction Memory ",
      "Instruction Memory -> Control Unit -> Register File -> ALU -> Data Memory",
      "Control Unit -> Register File -> ALU -> Data Memory -> Instruction Memory "
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What is the Datapath Element that stores data for easy access?",
    answer: "Register",
    options: [
      "Register",
      "ALU",
      "Instruction Memory",
      "Control Unit"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What is the Datapath Element that stores instruction addresses?",
    answer: "Instruction Memory",
    options: [
        "Register",
        "ALU",
        "Instruction Memory",
        "Control Unit"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What is the Datapath Element that tells the processor what to use to process an instruction process it?",
    answer: "Control Unit",
    options: [
        "Register",
        "ALU",
        "Instruction Memory",
        "Control Unit"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: " What is the name of the Datapath Element that performs basic arithmetic?",
    answer: "ALU",
    options: [
        "Register",
        "ALU",
        "Instruction Memory",
        "Control Unit"
    ]
  },
  {
      //image 2
    numb: 7,
    question: "What is the value of RegDst when using control for ALU instructions? (open Q7 img in new tab)",
    answer: "1",
    options: [
        "0",
        "1",
        "16",
        "32"
    ]
  },
  {
      //image 3
    numb: 8,
    question: "What is the value of MemRead when using control for Store instructions? (open Q8 img in new tab)",
    answer: "0",
    options: [
        "16",
        "1",
        "8",
        "0"
    ]
  },
  {
      //image 4
    numb: 9,
    question: "What is the value of MemWrite when using control for Branch instructions? (open Q9 img in new tab)",
    answer: "1",
    options: [
        "16",
        "1",
        "8",
        "0"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which specialized register is the offset of a branch target address added to?",
    answer: "PC",
    options: [
        "$0",
        "PC",
        "SP",
        "A Specified Register"
    ]
  },
];